http://www.yellow.co.nz/terms/privacy-policy/

HomeProductsYellow ProfileSearch Engine OptimizationGoogle Search AdsGoogle Display AdsFacebook AdsMarketing Automation & CRMYellow PagesWhite PagesResourcesCustomer StoriesTips and ToolsYellow eBookFAQFlybuysAbout YellowOur teamCareersContact usFind a BusinessSign inCall usFollow usSkip to main contentProductsGet OnlineYellow ProfileSearch Engine OptimisationGet More CustomersGoogle Search AdsGoogle Display AdsFacebook AdsDo Business BetterMarketing Automation & CRMPrint DirectoriesYellow PagesWhite PagesResourcesCustomer StoriesTips and ToolsYellow eBookFAQFlybuysAbout YellowOur TeamCareersContact UsFind a businessSign upSign inPrivacy PolicyWe are committed to protecting the privacy of information you might provide via any of our websites or mobile applications (each a Property and together the Properties), or otherwise. This policy (Privacy Policy) explains how Yellow NZ Limited (we, us, our) manage your information. 1 - Consent to Privacy Policy1.1 - By using a Property, engaging us to provide products and/or services and/or submitting personal information to us, you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, and consent to the use, collection, disclosure and retention of personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. 2 - Your information2.1 - You acknowledge and agree that we may in the course of operating our business collect information about you. This may be: a                provided by you;b               obtained or derived from Property usage information (whether through tracking your click behaviour or otherwise);c                obtained or derived from aggregated data not relating to you personally, such as the measuring of traffic relating to our Properties; and/or d               provided by third parties.2.2 - We may also require information about you so that we can provide our products and/or services to you and/or provide certain functionality on our Properties.  If you do not provide any information that we seek from you, we may not be able to provide such products, services and/or functionality. 3 - Use and sharing of information 3.1 - You acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use your information to: a                generally operate our business;b               provide you and others with, and improve, our Properties, products and services;c               inform you about our Properties, products and services, and any changes thereof;d               administer our contests, promotions, surveys and other services;e               obtain your feedback or views about our Properties, products and services;f                respond to any queries, feedback or other correspondence from you;g               gain an understanding of your needs;h               prevent and detect any misuse of, or fraudulent activities involving, any of our Properties, products or services;i                 maintain and develop our business systems and infrastructure, including testing and upgrading of these systems; and/orj                 provide to third parties for targeted advertising. 3.2 - You acknowledge and agree that personal information may be shared with our officers, employees, contractors, agents, professional advisors, our related companies, and third parties (including our customers, suppliers or commercial partners) in relation to the purposes described above. We take reasonable steps to ensure that any third parties are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information.3.3 - We may also share your personal information as required by law, court order, regulatory authority or the listing rules of any stock exchange, to exercise our legal rights, in the event of a dispute or legal claim, and to defend against legal proceedings (threatened or actual).3.4 - You acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use non-personal information to:a                provide our customers or suppliers with marketing or promotional materials regarding our products and services; and/orb               assist our staff in providing tailored sales offers to our customers. 4 - Accessing and correcting your personal information4.1 - Under the Privacy Act 1993, you have rights of access to and correction of personal information that we hold in relation to you as an individual. There are certain grounds on which we may refuse access or correction requests (for example, where such information cannot be readily retrieved).  We may charge a fee to cover the costs of meeting your request.4.2 - To protect your privacy and the privacy of others, you accept that we may require you to verify your identity before we can give you access to, or change, your personal information.  Written requests for access and/or correction should be made by contacting us using the contact details set out in the ‘Contact us’ section below. 5 - Links5.1 - Our Properties may provide links to other websites or mobile applications. Please note that such destinations may have different security and privacy policies. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for any information that you divulge to such destinations or how their owners or operators collect, use or disclose such information.  You should exercise caution and look at the privacy policy applying to such destination in question. You acknowledge that we are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of any third party (including third parties to whom we are permitted to disclose your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable laws). 6 - Cookies6.1 - To help us provide the best possible services for users and customers, we collect and store information about the way our Properties are used (such as the number and type of electronic devices connecting to each Property, the location and any unique IDs provided by those devices, the operating systems and browsers used by those devices, and which parts of our Properties are being viewed or used). This may include sending a "cookie" to your device. A cookie is a message given to an internet browser by a web server. The browser stores the message in a text file. The message is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This identifies your device uniquely but does not harm your device and does not identify you.6.2 - Our Properties use one type of cookie for reporting on the use of a Property, and another type of cookie to provide you with certain functionality (such as displaying content that is relevant to you, or enabling you to retain search queries). Cookies will be sent to your device the first time you visit one of our Properties. If you do not wish to have a cookie placed on your device, please disable cookies via your internet browser’s settings menu. 7 - Advertisements7.1 - We may use a third-party provider, such as Google, Facebook and others, to serve advertising when you use our Properties. You acknowledge and agree that they may use your information and information about your use of our Properties in order to deliver customised advertising content and targeted advertising that may be of interest to you. When serving such advertisements, they may place, or recognise, a unique cookie on your device. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices for avoiding the use of your information, please visit https://support.google.com/adsense/troubleshooter/1631343 . 8 - Nielsen//NetRatings8.1 - We use the Nielsen//NetRatings counting system to track common entry and exit points for our Properties, compiling anonymous information about usage of our Properties, and randomly and anonymously surveying users of our Properties. To do this, our Properties may include a small piece of code on each page which accumulates these statistics. For more information and to view Nielson//Net Ratings’ privacy policy, please visit http://www.nielsen-online.com/corp.jsp?section=leg_prs . 9 - Personal information that is no longer required9.1 - We take reasonable steps to destroy, erase or permanently de-identity personal information as soon as practicable if it is no longer required by us. 10 - Security10.1 - We have reasonable safeguards in place to prevent theft, loss or unauthorised access, misuse, modification, disclosure or disposal of your personal information.  However, since no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure, you acknowledge and accept that we cannot and do not guarantee the security of information you transmit or receive through our Properties, and these activities are conducted at your own risk.  We cannot accept responsibility for misuse or loss of, or unauthorised access to, your personal information where the security of information is not within our control. 11 - Emails11.1 - By registering an account with us via our Properties or by providing us with your email address, you consent to receiving commercial emails from us or on our behalf, from our related companies and/or from third parties, unless you expressly reject such consent at that time, or until you opt-out of receiving such commercial emails by using the unsubscribe facility provided therein or via certain of our Properties. We may always send you non-commercial emails. 12 - Terms of Use12.1 - Our Terms of Use  apply in addition to this Privacy Policy. In the event of any conflict between this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, the Terms of Use prevail to the extent permitted at law. 13 - Changes13.1 - We may, at our discretion, update or revise this Privacy Policy, by adding, changing or removing terms at any time. Any changes will take effect immediately from the time it is published on the relevant Property, so we encourage you to periodically check from time to time to see if this Privacy Policy has changed. Your continued use of a Property confirms your acceptance of its terms including any amendments. 14 - Contact us14.1 - If you have any questions about the privacy of your personal information please contact us .
